Michael Moloughney

Web Developer

A self-motivated, solutions-based programmer with an extensive knowledge of multiple programming languages and frameworks. Capable of working with a variety of technology and software solutions, and managing databases. Valuable team member who has experience diagnosing problems and developing solutions.

240 Main Street Apt 215 Little Falls, NJ 07424 (201)-956-8764 mmoloughney@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

MIS Implants USA, Fair Lawn, NJ — Lead Developer/DBA

JUNE 2014 - PRESENT

- Developed both internal and external websites/tools to help with sales, inventory, financial and customer service needs.
- Managed and supported all reporting needs within the company. Developed within, as well as implementing complementary reporting around our ERP.
- Worked hand in hand with all departments to facilitate data transfers between departments.

IpiggiBank, Paramus, NJ — Web Developer

SEPTEMBER 2013-JUNE 2014

• Helped develop a custom website for a startup educational banking service.

EDUCATION

William Paterson University, Wayne, NJ — Bachelor of Computer Science

SEPTEMBER 2012 - MAY 2014

- Graduated Magna Cum Laude.
- Member of Computer Science Honor Society.

LANGUAGES/FRAMEWORKS

Javascript | React, Mithril.js

C# | ASP.NET MVC

Python | Flask

SQL

SOFTWARE

Visual Studio

Visual Studio Code

SQL Server Studio Managen

Excel

SAP B1

PROJECTS

MDX — Digital implant planning and tracking website

Languages/Frameworks used:

- ASP.NET MVC backend
- Vuejs frontend

<u>MIS Implants Payment Portal</u> —Web interface for convenient client payments

Languages/Frameworks used:

- Laravel(PHP) backend
- Vuejs frontend

MyMis — Webclient for office and sales employees to access documentation and marketing materials.

Languages/Frameworks

- Laravel(PHP)
- Mithril.js and Vue.js frontend